Thor Wessel Lindberg

CONTACT

thorlindberg@icloud.com github.com/thorlindberg apple.com/developer/thor-lindberg

ABOUT ME

I'm a 25-year old junior developer and digital designer, passionate about design systems, software architecture, and mobile applications.

For the past 4+ years I have been writing in object-oriented programming languages, and the past 1+ year I have been developing eventand state-driven software projects.

LANGUAGES

Swift, JSX, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, Java, Visual Basic for Applications, Lua, SQL, XML

TOOLS & FRAMEWORKS

Xcode, Visual Studio Code, Git, GitLab, MATLAB, CSS, SwiftUI, UIKit, Streamlit, React, Bootstrap, Figma, Excel, Tableau, Cytoscape,

EDUCATION

MSc Information Technology (<u>cand.it</u>)

IT-University of Copenhagen, 2020-2022

BSc Health Information Science (<u>bach.sund.it</u>) Copenhagen University, 2017-2020

EXPERIENCE

Special Crime Unit (NSK)

IT-Administrative Student, 2021-2022 Financial Intelligence Unit

"In this role I was responsible for the frontend development, documentation and maintenance of our web portal, in addition to developing and advancing applications and tools for internal data retrieval, manipulation and encoding. Our team was split into pairs and tasks were assigned based on individual responsibilities."

IT-University of Copenhagen

Assistant Lecturer, 2022

UX Design II, Introduction to Programming

Teaching Assistant, 2021-2022

UX Design I, Introduction to Programming,

Experimental Design in Practice

"In these roles I was responsible for planning and conducting exercise sessions as an extension of lectures, and answering student questions about the curriculum, terminologies and assignments."

Domino's Pizza

Store Leader, 2021-2022 Domino's Lyngby

"In this role I was responsible for production and maintenance at our store, including inventory, payments, and delegating work to employees."